Vida Chenoweth collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series IV: Moving Images
  - Tanna Island music and dance, 1995-05, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV050)
    Tanna Island Lamakaun. Contents: Circumcision. Making Katum (percussion pouch). Commisioning a song. Nau dance.
  - Earth Drum, Part 1, 1995-06, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV051)
    Vanuatu. Mota Islands. Contents: Earth Drum, Part 1, filmed by Vida Chenoweth
  - Earth Drum contents, 1995-06, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV052)
    Vanuatu. Mota/Banks Islands. Contents: Constructing Earth Drum and Bamboo Slit-Drum. Women/men dancers.
  - Departure from Mota Island, 1995-06, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV053)
    Vanuatu. Mota Islands. Contents: Departure from Mota Island.
  - Cook Islands traditional song types, 1996-04, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV054)
    Cook Islands. Rarotonga. Contents: Traditional song types.
  - Musical Practices of Mota Island, 1995, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV055)
    Vanuatu. Mota Islands. Contents: Earth Drum. Musical Practices of Mota Island.
  - Earth Drum, Part 1, 1995, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV056)
    Vanuatu. Mota Islands. Contents: Earth Drum, part 1.
  - Earth Drum, Mota I, Part 2, 1995, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV057)
    Vanuatu. Mota Islands. Contents: Earth Drum, Mota I, Part 2.
  - Earth Drum, Mota I, Part 2, 1995, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV058)
  - Rarotongan Drum Dances, 1996, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV059)
    Cook Islands. Rarotonga.
  - Tanna Island Customs, 1996, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV060)
    Vanuatu. Tanna Islands.
  - Cook Islands Recording Project, "Imene Tuki," Part 1, 1996, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV061)
    Auckland.
  - Songs from the Cook Islands, Part 2, 1996, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV062)
  - Cook Islands Dance Lesson, 1996, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV063)
  - Cook Islands Recording Project, 1997, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV064)
    Cook Islands.
  - Cook Islands Recording Project, 1997, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV065)
    Cook Islands. Auckland. Contents: Imene Tuki, Part 1, Auckland. Part 2, Rarotonga.
  - Cook Islands Recording Project, 1997, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV066)
  - Romance with the Marimba, Vida Chenoweth film, 1999, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV067)
  - Shawn Dey's Senior Recital, undated, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV068)
  - Hall of Fame with Vida Chenoweth, 1985, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV069)
    Oklahoma. Wheaton College.
  - House dedication, Sio I, 1991, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV070)
    Papua New Guinea. Morobe Province.
  - Unidentified content, 1991, 1 videocassette (U-matic); V91/734 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV071)
  - Usarufas: Music from the Eastern Highlands, produced by John Caldwell, 1984, 1 videocassette (U-matic); F84/475 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV072)
  - Siassi sing-sing master, Part II, 1991, 1 videocassette (U-matic); F91/741 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV073)
    Papua New Guinea. Umboi Island. Ngauru village.
  - Siassi sing-sing master, Part I, 1991, 1 videocassette (U-matic); F91/741 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV074)
    Papua New Guinea. Umboi Island. Yangla village.
  - Vida revisits the Usarufa people, 1991, 1 videocassette (U-matic); F91/777 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV075)
    Papua New Guinea. Usarufa.
  - Students interns in Ethnomusicology presentations/recital, 1991, 1 videocassette (U-matic); F91/778 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV076)
    Ukarumpa/Bamu (Mopoda). Wheaton. People/language group: Sio.
  - Papua New Guinea Sing-Sing, Part I, 1991, 1 videocassette (U-matic); F91/779 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV077)
  - Papua New Guinea Sing-Sing, Part II, 1991, 1 videocassette (U-matic); F91/779 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: MV078)
  - Auyaana Survey #2, undated, 1 film reel, 8mm; .953 Auyf #2 (Film-id AFC 1994/003: MV079)
    Kaarite. Kaagu. Contents: Feast. Aayuraba.
  - Vida Chenoweth and Darlene Bee in Kaarite and Kaagu, undated, 1 film reel, 8mm; .953 Auyf #1 (Film-id AFC 1994/003: MV080)
    Kaarite. Kaagu. Contents: Port Moresby Lae (rainbow); Ukarumpa Land Rover to Kaagu; Bee returns after 3 years; Bee, Vida, Usarufas opening of Gadsup Council; Sing-Sing Kaagu; house building; making string bags; women gardening; road work; children; Kaarite; carrying Bee and pig; coffee skit of yaws; mock fight with shields; fence building; house building; child getting bath; roofing; children's play; melodica for transcribing (and "twinkle").
  - Sing-Sing, undated, 1 film reel, 8mm (Film-id AFC 1994/003: MV081)
    Sing-sing (Lae, Goroka, Koinautu).
  - Chenoweth family footage, undated, 1 DVD (Film-id AFC 1994/003: MV082)
    Disc 1 of 5. Children, teen, and preteen graduation.
  - Chenoweth and Green music store, undated, 1 DVD (Disc-id AFC 1994/003: MV083)
    Disc 2 of 5.
  - Chenoweth family films, undated, 1 DVD (Disc-id AFC 1994/003: MV084)
    Disc 3 of 5. Children as babies.
  - Vida Chenoweth's Command Performance for president of Guatemala, undated, 1 DVD (Disc-id AFC 1994/003: MV085)
    Disc 4 of 5.
  - Sing-Sing, 1 DVD (Disc-id AFC 1994/003: MV086)
    Disc 5 of 5. Papua New Guinea. Lae, Oroko, Kainautu Sing-Sing.